[
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "A cell uses which of the following to accelerate chemical reactions enabling its metabolic machinery to operate?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Centrasome",
      "b": "Lysosome",
      "c": "Golgi apparatus",
      "d": " Enzymes"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "The major parts of a cell are the ______________?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "surrounding membrane",
      "b": "surrounding membrane and cytoplasm",
      "c": "surrounding membrane, cytoplasm and nucleus",
      "d": "surrounding membrane, cytoplasm, nucleus and mitochondria"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "Light initiates different types of cellular reactions. Which of the following responses to light converts the energy from light into a gain of potential energy?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Phototaxis",
      "b": "Photoperiodism",
      "c": "Photosynthesis",
      "d": "All of the above"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "The functional unit of heredity is the _____________.",
    "answers": {
      "a": "gene",
      "b": "chromosome",
      "c": "protein",
      "d": "nucleus"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a"
  },
  {
    "type" : "input" , 
    "question": "DNA exists in the form of __________ strands of DNA coiled about each other.Number of them?",
    "answers": {

    },
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "There are two types of cells, eukaryotic and prokaryotic.",
    "answers": {
      "a": "True",
      "b": "False"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a"
  },
  {
    "type" : "input" , 
    "question": "How many chromosomes does an individual human person have?",
    "answers": {

    },
    "correctAnswer": "46"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "Sterile female honey bees are called _________________.",
    "answers": {
      "a": "drones",
      "b": "queen",
      "c": "guards",
      "d": "workers"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "In normal sexual reproduction, two mature germ cells fuse to form a _____________.",
    "answers": {
      "a": "gonad",
      "b": "ovary",
      "c": "embryogeny",
      "d": "zygote"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "Hybridization of animals from different species cannot occur.",
    "answers": {
      "a": "True",
      "b": "False"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b"
  },
  {
    "type" : "radio" , 
    "question": "Finish, good job!"

  }

]